<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Xinyi Shen</title>
    <link>http://ssxy00.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Xinyi Shen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 22:46:50 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://ssxy00.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Arxiv Daily | Nov 2021</title>
      <link>http://ssxy00.github.io/posts/arxiv-daily-2111/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 22:46:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ssxy00.github.io/posts/arxiv-daily-2111/</guid>
      <description>这篇博客记录的是 2021 年 11 月内刷到的 Arxiv cs.CL 感兴趣的文献。
12 Nov 21 &amp;ndash; 15 Nov 21 更新于 16 Nov 2021
Explainable Semantic Space by Grounding Language to Vision with Cross-Modal Contrastive Learning
 Author: Yizhen Zhang, Minkyu Choi, Kuan Han, Zhongming Liu Comments: Neurips 2021  ​
An Explanation of In-context Learning as Implicit Bayesian Inference
 Author: Sang Michael Xie, Aditi Raghunathan, Percy Liang, Tengyu Ma  ​
​
11 Nov 21 &amp;ndash; 12 Nov 21 更新于 15 Nov 2021</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arxiv Daily | Oct 2021</title>
      <link>http://ssxy00.github.io/posts/arxiv-daily-2110/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:53:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ssxy00.github.io/posts/arxiv-daily-2110/</guid>
      <description>这篇博客记录的是 2021 年 10 月内刷到的 Arxiv cs.CL 感兴趣的文献。
29 Oct 21 &amp;ndash; 1 Nov 21 更新于 9 Nov 2021
TransAug: Translate as Augmentation for Sentence Embeddings
 Author: Jue Wang, Haofan Wang, Xing Wu, Chaochen Gao, Debing Zhang  ​
EmpBot: A T5-based Empathetic Chatbot focusing on Sentiments
 Author: Emmanouil Zaranis, Georgios Paraskevopoulos, Athanasios Katsamanis, Alexandros Potamianos  ​
An Approach to Inference-Driven Dialogue Management within a Social Chatbot</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arxiv Daily | Sep 2021</title>
      <link>http://ssxy00.github.io/posts/arxiv-daily-2109/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 11:35:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ssxy00.github.io/posts/arxiv-daily-2109/</guid>
      <description>这篇博客记录的是 2021 年 9 月内刷到的 Arxiv cs.CL 感兴趣的文献。
29 Sep 21 &amp;ndash; 30 Sep 21 更新于 11 Oct 2021
None
​
​
28 Sep 21 &amp;ndash; 29 Sep 21 更新于 11 Oct 2021
Influence Patterns for Explaining Information Flow in BERT
 Author: Kaiji Lu, Zifan Wang, Piotr Mardziel, Anupam Datta Comments: Neurips 2021  ​
​
27 Sep 21 &amp;ndash; 28 Sep 21 更新于 29 Sep 2021
TURINGBENCH: A Benchmark Environment for Turing Test in the Age of Neural Text Generation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arxiv Daily | Jun 2021</title>
      <link>http://ssxy00.github.io/posts/arxiv-daily-2106/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 20:46:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ssxy00.github.io/posts/arxiv-daily-2106/</guid>
      <description>这篇博客记录的是 2021 年 6 月内刷到的 Arxiv cs.CL 感兴趣的文献。
30 Jun 21 &amp;ndash; 1 Jul 21 更新于 2 Aug 2021
All That’s ‘Human’ Is Not Gold: Evaluating Human Evaluation of Generated Text
 Author: Elizabeth Clark, Tal August, Sofia Serrano, Nikita Haduong, Suchin Gururangan, Noah A. Smith  ​
Controllable Open-ended Question Generation with A New Question Type Ontology
 Author: Shuyang Cao, Lu Wang Comments: ACL 2021  ​
CLINE: Contrastive Learning with Semantic Negative Examples for Natural Language Understanding</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arxiv Daily | Apr 2021</title>
      <link>http://ssxy00.github.io/posts/arxiv-daily-2104/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 08:45:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ssxy00.github.io/posts/arxiv-daily-2104/</guid>
      <description>这篇博客记录的是 2021 年 4 月内刷到的 Arxiv cs.CL 感兴趣的文献。
22 Apr 21 &amp;ndash; 23 Apr 21 更新于 11 May 2021
Interpreting Graph Neural Networks for NLP With Differentiable Edge Masking
 Author: Michael Sejr Schlichtkrull, Nicola De Cao, Ivan Titov Comments: ICLR 2021  ​
​
21 Apr 21 &amp;ndash; 22 Apr 21 更新于 4 May 2021
Provable Limitations of Acquiring Meaning from Ungrounded Form: What will Future Language Models Understand?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arxiv Daily | Mar 2021</title>
      <link>http://ssxy00.github.io/posts/arxiv-daily-2103/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 18:58:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ssxy00.github.io/posts/arxiv-daily-2103/</guid>
      <description>这篇博客记录的是 2021 年 3 月内刷到的 Arxiv cs.CL 感兴趣的文献。
31 Mar 21 &amp;ndash; 1 Apr 21 更新于 3 Apr 2021
Zero-Shot Language Transfer vs Iterative Back Translation for Unsupervised Machine Translation
 Author: Aviral Joshi, Chengzhi Huang, Har Simrat Singh  This work focuses on comparing different solutions for machine translation on low resource language pairs, namely, with zero-shot transfer learning and unsupervised machine translation.
​
Integrating Subgraph-aware Relation and DirectionReasoning for Question Answering</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arxiv Daily | Feb 2021</title>
      <link>http://ssxy00.github.io/posts/arxiv-daily-2102/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 18:57:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ssxy00.github.io/posts/arxiv-daily-2102/</guid>
      <description>这篇博客记录的是 2021 年 2 月内刷到的 Arxiv cs.CL 感兴趣的文献。
26 Feb 21 &amp;ndash; 1 Mar 21 更新于 23 Mar 2021
Learning Reasoning Paths over Semantic Graphs for Video-grounded Dialogues
 Author: Hung Le, Nancy F. Chen, Steven C.H. Hoi Comments: ICLR 2021  ​
OmniNet: Omnidirectional Representations from Transformers
 Author: Yi Tay, Mostafa Dehghani, Vamsi Aribandi, Jai Gupta, Philip Pham, Zhen Qin, Dara Bahri, Da-Cheng Juan, Donald Metzler  ​</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arxiv Daily | Jan 2021</title>
      <link>http://ssxy00.github.io/posts/arxiv-daily-2101/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 16:09:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ssxy00.github.io/posts/arxiv-daily-2101/</guid>
      <description>这篇博客记录的是 2021 年 1 月内刷到的 Arxiv cs.CL 感兴趣的文献。
29 Jan 21 &amp;ndash; 1 Feb 21 更新于 22 Feb 2021
Hierarchical Ranking for Answer Selection
 Author: Hang Gao, Mengting Hu, Renhong Cheng, Tiegang Gao  ​
Multilingual LAMA: Investigating Knowledge in Multilingual Pretrained Language Models
 Author: Nora Kassner, Philipp Dufter, Hinrich Schütze Comments: EACL 2021  &amp;lsquo;Working with mBERT, we investigate three questions. (i) Can mBERT be used as a multilingual knowledge base?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arxiv Daily | Dec 2020</title>
      <link>http://ssxy00.github.io/posts/arxiv-daily-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 10:15:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ssxy00.github.io/posts/arxiv-daily-2012/</guid>
      <description>这篇博客记录的是 2020 年 12 月内刷到的 Arxiv cs.CL 感兴趣的文献。
28 Dec 20 &amp;ndash; 31 Dec 20 更新于 11 Jan 2021
Robust Dialogue Utterance Rewriting as Sequence Tagging
 Author: Jie Hao, Linfeng Song, Liwei Wang, Kun Xu, Zhaopeng Tu, Dong Yu  dialogue utterance rewriting: The task aims to reconstruct the latest dialogue utterance into a new utterance that is semantically equivalent to the original one and can be understood without referring to the context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arxiv Daily | Nov 2020</title>
      <link>http://ssxy00.github.io/posts/arxiv-daily-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 12:57:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ssxy00.github.io/posts/arxiv-daily-2011/</guid>
      <description>这篇博客记录的是 2020 年 11 月内刷到的 Arxiv cs.CL 感兴趣的文献。
27 Nov 20 &amp;ndash; 30 Nov 20 更新于 2 Dec 2020
Latent Template Induction with Gumbel-CRFs
 Author: Yao Fu, Chuanqi Tan, Bin Bi, Mosha Chen, Yansong Feng, Alexander M. Rush Comments: NeurIPS 2020  ​
Generative Pre-training for Paraphrase Generation by Representing and Predicting Spans in Exemplars
 Author: Tien-Cuong Bui, Van-Duc Le, Hai-Thien To, Sang Kyun Cha Comments: IEEE International Conference on Big Data and Smart Computing 2021 Keywords: masking, predicting  ​</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>